Realization: I noticed that after I rebased, all the work I had done in the feature branch was added to the main branch history. As you can see, in the main branch the last logs were 6d1fe8b (main) Hotfix applied and a6393e6 Base commit. But after I ran git rebase main in the feature branch, it added 595e4b1 (HEAD -> feature) Extend feature and 2f1af3a Add feature. It’s like using push() in an array.

